*Music*
*Applause*
On behalf of myself and the board of directors and all of this evening's performers,
We thank you for joining us the evening and for supporting live music in the community.
We'd also like to give a special thanks to the library for this facility, the Meriden parks and recreaction department for rehearsal facility,
To Mary Moisuk for helping pass out programs tonight, to Mason Prigitano for his help with sound, photography and transportation tonight,
To Juliana Nesci for helping record the evening over here, to the Natle family for getting this on facebook tonight,
and Kelsey - she's one of our board members - for designing tonight's program,
and a special thank you to Anthony Susi for joining us this evening.  It was a pleasure doing one of his concert arrangements. *Applause*
And we thank you very much.  We hope you have a great summer and we hope to see you again in December.  Thank you!